<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Posts on maz.io</title><link>https://lucamazzanti.github.io/post/</link><description>Recent content in Posts on maz.io</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 07 Dec 2020 23:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://lucamazzanti.github.io/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Actually working on</title><link>https://lucamazzanti.github.io/post/works-in-progress-2020-12-08/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Dec 2020 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://lucamazzanti.github.io/post/works-in-progress-2020-12-08/</guid><description> Coding interview Design systems interview Complete Linux Training Course to Get Your Dream IT Job 2020 Mastering Docker - Fourth Edition</description></item><item><title>Introduction to encryption by Michael Pound</title><link>https://lucamazzanti.github.io/post/live-course-review-introduction-to-encryption/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 Nov 2020 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://lucamazzanti.github.io/post/live-course-review-introduction-to-encryption/</guid><description>This is the first review I do about courses or lectures, they are mostly notes and personal considerations I hope you like it. I start with a live course from O&amp;rsquo;Reilly learing platform that I really appreciate, there are a lot of courses taken by famous people, try it if you can.
Course: Introduction to encryption. A hands-on course on applying symmetric and asymmetric encryption. Relator: Michael Pound Publisher: O&amp;rsquo;Reilly live online training Duration: 3 hours Michael is a regular contributor to the popular YouTube channel Computerphile, where his videos on topics such as image analysis, machine learning, and computer security have accumulated over 30 million views from people all over the world.</description></item><item><title>Set up a static website with Hugo, Forestry and GitHub Pages</title><link>https://lucamazzanti.github.io/post/deploy-hugo-using-github-actions/</link><pubDate>Sat, 24 Oct 2020 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://lucamazzanti.github.io/post/deploy-hugo-using-github-actions/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;m moving a private knowledge base powered by WordPress to a public blog so I seized the opportunity to study a static site generator like Jekyll.
The generator: Hugo I chose Hugo one of the most popular generators, it&amp;rsquo;s really simple to use and to extend. Just download the CLI and run it in an empty folder and it will scaffold a basic site structure.
hugo new site quickstart Then it&amp;rsquo;s time to download a theme, put it in the themes folder and set the config.</description></item></channel></rss>